its a bright Friday morning and this is
the story of a happy and small family
it's the perfect day for an outing and
the Varma family has planned just that
the family is excited especially the
children
mrs. Varma is getting the delighted
children ready for the picnic while mr.
Varma heads out to check the car he
starts with the car checklist bonnet
check tires check trunk check fuel check
oops the car insurance policy has
expired the conventional way of renewing
the policy after an inspection will take
at least two days if they are lucky the
picnic is ruined the Varma family is
sulking and the children can't stop
crying
that's when mrs. Varma comes up with an
idea ICICI Lombard insurer app has a
self inspection option which helps you
get approval the quick easy and smart
way shortly mr. Varma gets a
notification inspection approved the
Varma family is off to enjoy their much
awaited picnic ICICI Lombard insurer
save the day for them
[Music]